{
  "author": "royal_flush",
  "rounds": [
    {
      "roundTitle": "The Tower of Babel",
      "questions": [
        {
          "questionText": "If you're splitting the bill equally in a restaurant, it's also known as going... what?",
          "correctAnswer": "Dutch"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Dijon mustard is also known as... what mustard?",
          "correctAnswer": "French"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "What is the official language of Brazil?",
          "correctAnswer": "Portuguese"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "In Monty Python, nobody expects what type of inquisition?",
          "correctAnswer": "Spanish"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "In Watership Down, what language is used by rabbit characters?",
          "correctAnswer": "Lapine"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "What is the official language of the country that was home to Alfred Nobel?",
          "correctAnswer": "Swedish"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "From which language do we get the phrase 'Hakuna Matata'?",
          "correctAnswer": "Swahili"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "What is the name of Tolkein's Elvish language used in the Lord of the Rings books?",
          "correctAnswer": "Quenya"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Pizza & pasta are two of the most common types of dish in which cuisine?",
          "correctAnswer": "Italian"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "If I was performing a traditional haka, what language would I be speaking?",
          "correctAnswer": "MƒÅori"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "In which language does the word hare translate to 'Hase'?",
          "correctAnswer": "German"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "What language is the mother tongue of Game of Thrones' Targaryen family?",
          "correctAnswer": "High Valyrian"
        }
      ],
      "redHerrings": [
        "Klingon",
        "Latin",
        "English",
        "Dothraki"
      ]
    },
    {
      "roundTitle": "Oo, Matron!",
      "questions": [
        {
          "questionText": "When I play Google That!, I really don't enjoy The Early Bird. I much prefer...",
          "correctAnswer": "Taboo"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Well, looks like we're heading for Lockdown 2: Electric...",
          "correctAnswer": "Boogaloo"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "You know what, Gmail is overrated. I'm switching back to...",
          "correctAnswer": "Yahoo"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "That bird is so pretty! It looks just like a parrot. Yeah, it's a...",
          "correctAnswer": "Cockatoo"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "I keep the grand total of two bottles in the bathroom. One is shower gel, the other is...",
          "correctAnswer": "Shampoo"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "I can never remember the name of that really catchy ABBA song. Oh hang on, it's...",
          "correctAnswer": "Waterloo"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Origin of Symmetry was pretty good, but I much prefer Muse's live album...",
          "correctAnswer": "Hullabaloo"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "I can get the saddle on there, but whenever I go for the cowboy hat, it goes off. That's why I don't play...",
          "correctAnswer": "Buckaroo"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "My favourite song from The Jungle Book is definitely one of the ones sung by...",
          "correctAnswer": "Baloo"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "That's the cutest dog I've ever seen. Thanks, it's a Cocker Spaniel/Poodle cross, more commonly known as a...",
          "correctAnswer": "Cockapoo"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "This 1080Ti is pretty good, but I remember the days of...",
          "correctAnswer": "Voodoo"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "A korma?! What's the point in even having a curry? I'm gonna be having a chicken...",
          "correctAnswer": "Vindaloo"
        }
      ],
      "redHerrings": [
        "Tattoo",
        "Bamboo",
        "Peekaboo",
        "Cuckoo"
      ]
    },
    {
      "roundTitle": "Stars & Stripes",
      "questions": [
        {
          "questionText": "Which of these is the title of a 1975 musical about female prison inmates?",
          "correctAnswer": "Chicago"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Where was home to the characters from the sitcoms Friends, Sienfeld & How I Met Your Mother?",
          "correctAnswer": "New York"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Finish the 1993 film title: Sleepless in...",
          "correctAnswer": "Seattle"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Hollywood is a neighbourhood in the central region of which city?",
          "correctAnswer": "Los Angeles"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "What is the capital city of the state of Texas?",
          "correctAnswer": "Austin"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "In which city would you find the Golden Gate Bridge?",
          "correctAnswer": "San Francisco"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "CSI had spin-off series' set in New York and which other city?",
          "correctAnswer": "Miami"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "What is the capital city of the USA?",
          "correctAnswer": "Washington D.C"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Complete the title of the 1971 book by Hunter S. Thompson: Fear & Loathing in...",
          "correctAnswer": "Las Vegas"
        }
      ],
      "redHerrings": [
        "Philadelphia",
        "Dallas",
        "Phoenix"
      ]
    },
    {
      "roundTitle": "Oscar Bait",
      "questions": [
        {
          "questionText": "Identify six films that won six or more Academy Awards",
          "correctAnswer": "The Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King (2003)"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Identify six films that won six or more Academy Awards",
          "correctAnswer": "The English Patient (1966)"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Identify six films that won six or more Academy Awards",
          "correctAnswer": "Slumdog Millionaire (2008)"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Identify six films that won six or more Academy Awards",
          "correctAnswer": "Star Wars (1977)"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Identify six films that won six or more Academy Awards",
          "correctAnswer": "Gravity (2013)"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Identify six films that won six or more Academy Awards",
          "correctAnswer": "Amadeus (1984)"
        }
      ],
      "redHerrings": [
        "The Thief of Bagdad (1940)",
        "Avatar (2009)",
        "There Will Be Blood (2007)",
        "The Revenant (2015)",
        "The King's Speech (2010)",
        "The Godfather (1972)",
        "Brokeback Mountain (2005)",
        "The Exorcist (1973)",
        "A Streetcar Named Desire (1951)",
        "Joker (2019)"
      ]
    }
  ]
}